(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Blue Journey 1st Live 「夜明けのうた」
Blue Journey 1st Live: Dawn's Song
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ①
Blue Journey 1st Live: Made-to-order Goods 1
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ②
Blue Journey 1st Live: Made-to-order Goods 2
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ③
Blue Journey 1st Live: Made-to-order Goods 3
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ④
Blue Journey 1st Live: Made-to-order Goods 4
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ⑤
Blue Journey 1st Live: Made-to-order Goods 5
3Dアクリルスタンド Blue Journey衣装ver.
3D Acrylic Stand: Blue Journey Costume ver.
「夜明けのうた」をよりお楽しみいただくために
To help you enjoy "Dawn's Song" even more:
Blue Journeyの今回の旅は、歌と朗読で紡いだ、ひとつの物語のようなライブです。
This journey is a live performance like a single story, woven from song and recitation.
短い旅ではございますが、心に残る体験をしていただきたいと考えています。
Though it is a short journey, we hope it will be an unforgettable experience for you.
旅に間に合うよう、時間に余裕を持ったご準備をお願いいたします。
Please prepare with plenty of time so you can join the journey on schedule.
#夜明けのBJライブ
#DawnBJLive
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the show starts.
Blue Journey 1st Live 「夜明けのうた」
Blue Journey 1st Live "Aoake no Uta"
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ①
Blue Journey 1st Live Order Goods ①
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ②
Blue Journey 1st Live Order Goods ②
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ③
Blue Journey 1st Live Order Goods ③
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ④
Blue Journey 1st Live Order Goods ④
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ⑤
Blue Journey 1st Live Order Goods ⑤
3Dアクリルスタンド Blue Journey 衣装ver.
3D Acrylic Stand Blue Journey Costume ver.
「夜明けのうた」をよりお楽しみいただくために
To enjoy "Aoake no Uta" even more
Blue Journey 1st Live 夜明けのうた #夜明けのBJライブ
Blue Journey 1st Live Aoake no Uta #AoakeNoBJLive
推しの曲、めっちゃいいな。
My favorite's song is so good.
みるハコ
Miru Hako
チャンス！
Chance!
みるハコなら、臨場感たっぷりで
With Miru Hako, it's full of realism...
推しのコンテンツが楽しめる！
...and you can enjoy your favorite's content!
みるハコ最高！
Miru Hako is the best!
オトモ増やそう。
Let's get more buddies.
みるハコ by JOYSOUND
Miru Hako by JOYSOUND
Blue Journey 1st Live 「夜明けのうた」
Blue Journey 1st Live: Song of Dawn
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ①
Blue Journey 1st Live Pre-order Goods 1
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ②
Blue Journey 1st Live Pre-order Goods 2
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ③
Blue Journey 1st Live Pre-order Goods 3
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ④
Blue Journey 1st Live Pre-order Goods 4
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ⑤
Blue Journey 1st Live Pre-order Goods 5
3Dアクリルスタンド Blue Journey 衣装ver.
3D Acrylic Stand: Blue Journey Outfit ver.
「夜明けのうた」をよりお楽しみいただくために
To better enjoy "Song of Dawn"
Blue Journeyの今回の旅は、歌と朗読で紡いだ、ひとつの物語のようなライブです。
Blue Journey's current journey is a live show like a single story, woven together by song and recitation.
短い旅ではございますが、心に残る体験をしていただきたいと考えています。
Though it's a short journey, we hope it will be a memorable experience for you.
旅に間に合うよう、時間に余裕を持ったご準備をお願いいたします。
Please prepare in advance with plenty of time so you can make it to the journey.
Blue Journey 1st Live 夜明けのうた
Blue Journey 1st Live: Yoake no Uta
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ①
Blue Journey 1st Live: Order-made goods 1
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ②
Blue Journey 1st Live: Order-made goods 2
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ③
Blue Journey 1st Live: Order-made goods 3
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ④
Blue Journey 1st Live: Order-made goods 4
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ⑤
Blue Journey 1st Live: Order-made goods 5
3Dアクリルスタンド Blue Journey衣装ver.
3D Acrylic Stand: Blue Journey Costume ver.
「夜明けのうた」をよりお楽しみいただくために
To help you enjoy "Yoake no Uta" even more
Blue Journeyの今回の旅は、歌と朗読で紡いだ、
Blue Journey's journey this time is a live performance
ひとつの物語のようなライブです。
woven with song and recitation, like a single story.
短い旅ではございますが、心に残る体験を
Although it is a short trip, we want to provide you
していただきたいと考えています。
with a memorable experience.
旅に間に合うよう、時間に余裕を持った
Please prepare with plenty of time to spare
ご準備をお願いいたします。
so that you can make it in time for the journey.
推しの曲、めっちゃいい。
My favorite's song is so good.
みるハコ、チャーンス！
Miruhako Chance!
みるハコなら、大画面、大音量で、
With Miruhako, on a large screen at high volume,
推しのコンテンツが楽しめる。
you can enjoy your favorite content.
みるハコ最高！
Miruhako is the best!
音もやばそう！
The sound is going to be amazing too!
JOYSOUND
Blue Journey 1st Live 受注グッズ
Blue Journey 1st Live Pre-order Goods
「夜明けのうた」をよりお楽しみいただくために
To enjoy "Song of Dawn" even more
本日は、Blue Journey 1st ライブ「夜明けのうた」にご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to Blue Journey 1st Live "Yoake no Uta" today.
開演に先立ちまして、お客様にご注意並びにご案内申し上げます。
Prior to the performance, we have some precautions and information for you.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, audio recording, and the use of video recording equipment are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮くださいますようお願い申し上げます。
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue. We ask that you refrain from smoking.
万が一、体調に異変を感じる場合には、無理をせず係員へお申し出ください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not overdo it and inform a staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、肩車、ステージ上に物を投げ込む、
Moshing, diving, shoulder rides, throwing objects onto the stage,
ステージ上に上がる、故意に通路を塞ぐ、前に押し寄せる、
getting onto the stage, intentionally blocking aisles, pushing forward,
周りのお客様のご迷惑となるような不自然なコール、姿勢、公演の妨げとなる大きな音を鳴らすなどの行為、
unnatural calls, postures, or making loud noises that disturb others or the performance,
不自然なタイミングで両手を左右に激しく振る、腕を振り回す、上半身を反らすなどの過激な応援行為、
extreme cheering such as violent hand waving at unnatural times, swinging arms, or bending backwards,
過度なジャンプ行為など、他のお客様のご迷惑になる、または公演を妨げる禁止行為は一切禁止です。
and excessive jumping or any other acts that disturb others or the performance are strictly prohibited.
本公演は映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席のお客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。
Cameras for streaming and photography will be present, and audience members may be captured in the footage.
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please note that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
それでは、まもなく開演いたします。お席についてお待ちください。
The performance will begin shortly. Please remain in your seats.
Blue Journeyの今回の旅は、歌と朗読で紡いだ、一つの物語のようなライブです。
Blue Journey's journey this time is a live concert like a story, woven together with songs and readings.
短い旅ではございますが、皆様の心に残る体験を、皆様と一緒に作っていきたいと考えています。
It's a short journey, but we'd like to create an experience that remains in your hearts together with all of you.
Blue Journeyの今回の旅は、歌と朗読で紡いだ、一つの物語のようなライブです。
Blue Journey's journey this time is a live concert like a story, woven together with songs and readings.
短い旅ではございますが、皆様の心に残る体験を、皆様と一緒に作っていきたいと考えています。
It's a short journey, but we'd like to create an experience that remains in your hearts together with all of you.
これに際して、会場の皆様にお願いがございます。
Regarding this, we have a request for the audience here at the venue.
静かなパートなどで激しい声援を送るなど、演出の妨げとなるような応援はお控えください。
Please refrain from cheering in ways that interfere with the production, such as loud cheering during quiet parts.
また、ペンライトは、青や白など、Blue Journeyを表す色を主に使って応援をお願いいたします。
Also, please use penlights mainly in colors that represent Blue Journey, such as blue or white.
もちろんこれは、推しカラーや曲の照明演出に沿った応援を一律に禁止するものではございません。
Of course, this does not uniformly prohibit cheering according to your favorite member's color or the lighting for the song.
なお、オープニングに際しては、1曲目の歌が始まるまではぜひペンライトを消してお楽しみください。
For the opening, please turn off your penlights until the first song begins.
曲が始まりましたら、ペンライトを付けて、
Once the song starts, please turn on your penlights,
そこからは主に青や白など、Blue Journeyの色を使い、全力で応援をしてください。
And from then on, please cheer with all your might using mainly Blue Journey's colors like blue and white.
それでは、Blue Journey 1st Live「夜明けのうた」をお楽しみください。
Now, please enjoy Blue Journey 1st Live "Song of Dawn."
僕らは、どうして生きているのだろう。
Why are we living?
僕らは、どうして笑っているのだろう。
Why are we laughing?
僕らは、どうして怒っているのだろう。
Why are we angry?
僕らは、どうして...
Why are we...
誤魔化したり...
Deceiving ourselves...
悩んだり
Worrying,
嘘をついたり
lying,
強がったり
acting tough,
素直になれなかったり
not being able to be honest,
迷ったり
getting lost,
信じなかったり
not believing,
矛盾したり
contradicting,
言えなかったり
not being able to say it,
傷つけあったり
hurting each other,
無くしてしまったり
losing things,
気づかないふりをしたり
pretending not to notice.
どうしてそんなことをするんだろう。
I wonder why we do such things.
ただ一緒にいたいだけなのに
Even though I just want to be with you,
ただ好きでいたいだけなのに
even though I just want to keep loving you,
ただ楽しくいたいだけなのに
even though I just want to have fun.
繰り返す日々に感情がすり潰されて
My emotions are worn down by the repeating days,
行ったり来たりする毎日に嫌気がさして
and I'm sick of the days going back and forth.
怒りをぶつける言い訳にいつも誰かを使ったりしてる
I'm always using someone as an excuse to vent my anger.
そんな人間が嫌いだ
I hate people like that.
そんな世界が嫌いだ
I hate a world like that.
そんなあいつらが大嫌いだ
I hate those people.
そんな僕も大嫌いだ
I hate myself too.
大嫌いだ
I hate it all.
大嫌いなはずなのに
I'm supposed to hate it,
壊してしまうのが怖かった
but I was afraid of breaking it.
守りたかったはずなのに
I was supposed to want to protect it,
傷つくことが怖かった
but I was afraid of getting hurt.
大好きだったはずなのに
I was supposed to love it,
離れ離れになってしまった
but we've become separated.
あの時 声を上げていれば
If I had raised my voice then,
あの時 話し合っていれば
if we had talked things over then,
あの時 ちゃんと伝えていれば
if I had conveyed it properly then,
何かが変わっただろうか
would something have changed?
これは そんな僕の物語
This is my story.
愛想笑いで誤魔化してた 本当のこと言えなかった
I was hiding it with a fake smile, I couldn't tell the truth.
大切なものを見落とした 僕は独りだ
I overlooked what was important, I am alone.
敷かれたレールの 上を走って
Running on top of the laid out rails,
またほら今日も 同じ道
look, it's the same road again today.
通り過ぎてゆく 景色を見て
Looking at the scenery passing by,
自分から目を逸らす
I look away from myself.
そうじゃない
That's not it.
こんなはずじゃなかったなぁ
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
そうだろ そうだろ 言い聞かせてた
Right? Right? I kept telling myself.
不安定さ
Unsteadiness.
後悔の連続ばかりで 失ってばかりなんだ
Just a series of regrets, I'm just losing things.
失敗も後悔も全部 やり直したいのに
Failure, regret, everything, I want to start over,
失って初めて気づいた 与えられてばかりの僕だ
but I only realized after losing it, I've just been given everything.
ああ だから僕は独りだ
Ah, that's why I'm alone.
あの日の後悔が 今日もよぎる
That day's regret crosses my mind today too.
今でもずっと 繰り返し
Even now, over and over.
窓辺の景色に 思いを留めて
Keeping my thoughts on the scenery by the window,
日常に目を逸らす
I look away from everyday life.
いつまで
Until when?
ずっとこのままなの？
Will it be like this forever?
どうして どうして 分かり合えずに
Why? Why? Without being able to understand each other,
いつまでも
forever.
失敗の連続ばかりで 間違ってばかりなんだ
Just a series of failures, I'm just making mistakes.
人生も関係も全部 やり直したいのに
Life, relationships, everything, I want to start over,
間違って初めて気づいた 諦めてばかりの僕だ
but I only realized after making mistakes, I've just been giving up.
ああ だから今もこのまま
Ah, that's why I'm still like this.
救いさえ 灰になる
Even salvation turns to ash.
霞んでゆく過去 傷口と幻
The fading past, wounds and illusions.
痛みも忘れてしまうなら
If I'm going to forget the pain too,
思い出すよ ここにあったと だから僕
I'll remember, that it was here, that's why I...
チラ見せパートは間も無く終了です
続きは配信プラットフォーム「Z-aN」,「SPWN」でご視聴ください
The free preview part will end shortly.
Please watch the rest on streaming platforms 'Z-aN' or 'SPWN'.
後悔の連続ばかりで
A succession of regrets,
失ってばかりだった
and all I did was lose things.
失敗も後悔も全部
The failures and the regrets, all of them...
やり直したいんだ
I want to start them all over.
今更始めて気づいた
I've only just realized it now.
いつだって馬鹿な僕だ
I've always been such a fool.
ああ...
Ah...
だから 僕は独りだ
That's why I'm all alone.
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!